// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "In badminton, how many players are there in a doubles match?",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The shuttlecock used in badminton has feathers and a cork base. What is it called?",
    answer: "Birdie",
    options: [
      "Ball",
      "Shuttle",
      "Birdie",
      "Shuttlecock"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the highest score a player can achieve in a single serve in badminton?",
    answer: "15",
    options: [
      "10",
      "15",
      "20",
      "30"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "When was badminton officially included in the Summer Olympics?",
    answer: "1992",
    options: [
      "1980",
      "1992",
      "2000",
      "2016"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How many points are needed to win a standard game of badminton?",
    answer: "21",
    options: [
      "11",
      "15",
      "21",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the name of the shot in badminton where the shuttlecock is hit forcefully downward into the opponent's court?",
    answer: "Smash",
    options: [
      "Smash",
      "Drive",
      "Dropshot",
      "Clear"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the purpose of the backhand grip in badminton?",
    answer: "To improve control and accuracy",
    options: [
      "To increase power in shots",
      "To improve control and accuracy",
      "To confuse the opponent",
      "To facilitate serving",
    
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How many times is a player allowed to hit the shuttlecock on their side of the net during a rally in badminton?",
    answer: "Unlimited",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "Unlimited"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "In badminton, what is it called when the server's feet do not remain stationary during the serve?",
    answer: "Fault",
    options: [
      "Fault",
      "Let",
      "Replay",
      "Ace"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which country is historically dominant in badminton and has won the most Olympic gold medals in the sport?",
    answer: "China",
    options: [
      "US",
      "China",
      "India",
      "Malaysia"
    ]
  },

 
];